okay we've seen some results on the
好吧，我们已经看到了一些结果
difficulties associated with aggregating
与汇总相关的困难
preferences coherently and what I want
连贯的偏好和我想要的
to do is talk a little bit about the
要做的是谈论一些
setting where things are nicely behaved
设定事情表现良好的地方
and these are known as single peaked
这些被称为单峰
preferences and sometimes voters
偏好，有时还有选民
preferences have nice properties and a
首选项具有不错的属性和
very prominent case of that is when
当时最突出的情况是
candidates connect should be ordered
候选人应联系
from left to right so we can think of
从左到右，所以我们可以想到
leftmost candidates right most
最左边的候选人最右边
candidates and candidates can be nicely
候选人和候选人可以很好
ordered and in situations where people
在有秩序的情况下
have a most preferred outcome or
有最理想的结果或
candidate on this spectrum then
那么这个范围的候选人
candidates are going to have nice
候选人会很高兴
properties in terms of existing having
就现有的财产而言
an existing condor sale in ER having
ER中现有的秃鹰销售
nicely defined voting schemes and so
定义明确的投票方案等等
forth and so the idea here is is people
来，所以这里的想法是人
have a most preferred point and they
有一个最喜欢的观点，他们
prefer candidates closest to that and
更喜欢与之最接近的候选人
don't prefer ones that are further away
不喜欢离得更远的人
now you know we can think of this in a
现在您知道我们可以在一个
political spectrum you could also think
您还可以想到的政治范围
of you know how much tax would you like
你们当中的人知道您想要多少税
to have well people might have an
拥有良好的人可能会
optimal tax rate and and not like to
最佳税率，并且不喜欢
have higher tax rates or lower tax rates
具有较高的税率或较低的税率
or what's the extent of some regulation
或什么程度的监管
we can think of a series of different
我们可以想到一系列不同的
settings where we have a nice ordering
设置好点的地方
over the alternatives and people's
在替代品和人们的
preferences are going to have this
喜好将有这个
property so in particular when we think
财产，特别是当我们认为
about you know so our set of outcomes
关于你知道，所以我们的结果
let's say our set of outcomes here is a
假设我们这里的结果是
b c d e and we look at a person who has
bcde，我们看一个有
single preferences we look at say the
我们看一个单一的偏好说
utility so here the utility the payoff
效用，所以这是效用的回报
they get from a given alternative and
他们从给定的选择中获得
their most preferred alternative in this
他们最喜欢的替代品
case is b they get the highest and then
情况是b他们得到最高，然后
when we look at the other alternatives
当我们看其他选择时
in this case c would be second highest a
在这种情况下，c将是第二高的a
would be third highest then D and then e
将是第三高，然后是D，然后是e
is way down here so their preferences
不在这里，所以他们的喜好
would look like b c d e in terms of a
看起来像bcde
ranking but what's important in terms of
排名，但重要的是
single peakedness is that the further
单峰化是
you move this way the lower the
您向下方移动
Preferences the the
首选项
lower the utility is so the voter always
降低效用，所以选民总是
prefers something which is closer to be
喜欢更接近的东西
than something further away on the same
比同一事物更远的东西
side and similarly the more you move in
侧面，同样，您越往内走
this direction the voter prefers the
这个方向，选民更喜欢
alternative B to a or anything further
B替代a或其他
to the left of a so that's what's known
在左侧，这就是已知的
as a single peak preference and the fact
作为单峰偏好和事实
that you've got this nice ordering and
您的订单很好，
it can be ordered on the line with the
可以与
most preferred alternative and things
最喜欢的替代品和东西
getting worse when you move away that
当你离开那会变得更糟
kind of preference means that you've got
某种偏好意味着您已经
nice voting procedures and the existence
良好的投票程序和存在
of cuando se winners so let's have a
的cuando se获奖者，让我们来
peek at that just understand why things
偷看那个，只是明白为什么事情
are going to be better behaved in this
在这方面会表现得更好
kind of world so imagine we had three
这样的世界，想象我们有三个
voters that have single peaked
单身高峰的选民
preferences and we had our ABCDE
偏好，我们有了ABCDE
so we'll keep an odd number of voters to
所以我们要让奇数选民参加
make sure we don't have to worry about
确保我们不必担心
ties what's true then is if we look at
联系我们，那么真正的意义是
the median most preferred outcome that's
中位数最优选的结果是
going to be a Condorcet winner so in
将会成为Condorcet的赢家，所以
this case that's B so B's most preferred
这种情况是B，所以B是最优选的
by this middle person so let's call this
这个中间人，所以我们称之为
person 1 person 2 person three person 3
人1人2人三人3
is most preferred alternative is D
最优选的替代方法是D
person ones most preferred alternative
人的首选
is a and let's verify that this outcome
是一个，让我们验证一下这个结果
B is actually going to beat everything
B实际上将击败一切
in a pairwise comparison so suppose we
在成对比较中，假设我们
compare B to C well both persons 1 & 2
将B和C分别比较1和2
like be better than C they also like it
喜欢比C更好，他们也喜欢
better than D and E right so given the
比D和E好，所以给定
fact that we've got we look at the when
事实上，我们看到了什么时候
we look at the median voters all the
我们看看中位数选民
voters to the left of the median are
中位数左侧的选民是
going to prefer the median speak to any
将倾向于中位数对任何人说话
alternative which lies to the right
右边的选择
because going to the right further to
因为去右边
the right is bad and similarly we're
权利是坏的，同样地我们
going to have a majority of people on
将会有大多数人
the right preferring the medians
偏爱中位数的权利
alternative to anything that's to the
替代一切
left of the the medians alternate the
中位数的左侧交替
medians most preferred alternative so
中位数是最优选的替代方案，因此
the median outcome here median outcome
这里的中位数结果
is a Condorcet winner median
是Condorcet赢家的中位数
median peak here right so we look at the
这里的中值峰值是正确的，所以我们看一下
peak we look at the meeting of the peaks
高峰我们看峰会
that's a condor say winner and so we're
这是秃鹰说的赢家，所以我们
going to have a well-defined alternative
将有一个明确的替代方案
which is going to beat every other one
这将击败其他人
and this gives us a nice way of choosing
这为我们提供了一种不错的选择方式
an alternative it's known as median
另一种方法叫做中位数
voting and it gives us an idea of why we
投票，这让我们知道为什么
always talk about median voters and so
总是谈论中位数选民，所以
forth because then we've got a majority
来吧，因为那时我们得到了大多数
that prefers that position to anything
比任何东西都更喜欢那个位置
on the other side and and vice versa we
另一方面，反之亦然
have a condo say winner
有公寓说赢家
moreover this is going to have nice
而且这会很好
properties in terms of people
以人为单位的财产
misrepresenting their preferences right
歪曲他们的偏好权利
so could to improve by changing their
因此可以通过改变他们的
ordering know their their alternative is
订购知道他们的选择是
picked right be their favorite artery
选对了他们最喜欢的动脉
let's think about person a how could you
让我们考虑一个人，你怎么可能
affect this by by if your median voting
通过您的中位数投票来影响
we're picking the meeting of the three
我们正在挑选三个人的会议
alternatives so if we think about
替代方案，所以如果我们考虑
picking the median alternative of these
选择这些的中位数替代方案
three alternatives then the only way
那么只有三种选择
that person one could affect the outcome
这个人可能会影响结果
would be to change the median how could
将会改变中位数
they change the median they would have
他们改变了中位数
to announce a peak over here C D or E
宣布此处CD或E达到峰值
and all of those alternatives are worse
所有这些选择都更糟
than B so there's by misrepresenting the
比B，因此存在误解
preferences this person person one would
这个人一个人的喜好
actually do worse so this is in you can
实际上更糟，所以这可以
verify that that's also true for three
验证三个人也是如此
or any individual the only way you're
或任何个人，唯一的方式
going to be able to make a difference is
能够有所作为的是
to change the median which means you
改变中位数，这意味着你
have to flip to the other side which is
必须翻转到另一边
something you're generally not going to
通常你不会去做的事情
want to do so nice thing about single
想要对单身做一件好事
peak preference world's median most
最高偏好世界中位数
preferred point is a Condorcet winner
首选点是Condorcet赢家
and individuals are going to have
和个人将有
incentives to be truthful and to
诚实和激励的动机
announce their preferences in a truthful
诚实地宣布自己的喜好
manner in fact it's going to be a
实际上，这将是一个
dominant strategy if we ask people for
主导策略，如果我们要求人们
their preferences to announce their
他们的喜好宣布
truthful preference if we're using
如果我们使用真实的偏好
majority voting
多数投票
I'm sorry median voting in this case so
我很抱歉在这种情况下的中位数投票
there are settings where a lot of the
在某些设置中，
negative results of impossibilities of
不可能的负面结果
aggregating preferences are overturned
总体偏好被推翻
and those are going to be ones where
那些将会成为
we've got a lot of structure on the
我们在结构上有很多
problem and that structure the problem
问题和那个结构问题
means we have nice order
意味着我们的订单很好
and there's no voting cycles so this
而且没有投票周期，所以这
kind of setting there's no voting cycles
这种设置没有投票周期
we don't have the difficulties that
我们没有困难
underlie some of the issues like arrows
是某些问题的基础，例如箭头
theorem and so forth once we go into
定理等等，一旦我们进入
this setting we have an icer set of
这个设置我们有一个冰柜
preferences in terms of the restrictions
限制方面的偏好
that they satisfy and that allows us to
他们满意，这使我们能够
aggregate preferences in ways that are
以下列方式汇总偏好
going to be nicely efficient strategy
将是非常有效的策略
proof having dominant strategies and so
有主导策略的证明等等
forth so there are settings which are
第四，因此有一些设置
quite natural where things are going to
很自然的地方
work out more more effectively than they
比他们更有效地锻炼
do when we allow for all preference
当我们允许所有偏好时执行
orderings over alternatives now when
现在在替代品上订购
that happens depends on the setting and
发生的情况取决于设置
there can be situations where you don't
在某些情况下您可能不会
have this nice left/right ordering so it
有这样好的左/右顺序，所以它
is a fairly restrictive setting but one
是一个相当严格的设置，但是
that at least captures a good number of
至少捕获了很多
applications
应用领域